beautycounter.com 2016-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Beautycounter

BeautyCounter is committed to maintaining the privacy of all visitors to our website, BeautyCounter.com (the “Site”), as described in this Privacy Statement.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION

When you visit our Site, we may collect certain personally identifiable information you knowingly choose to discloseto us, such as your name and email address. You may provide this information when you register with the Site, purchase products from the Site, or express interest in becoming a BeautyCounter representative or member.

BeautyCounter passively collects non-personal information that is automatically sent to us by your web browser or device including but not limited to your domain name and user name.

We may also collect aggregated information as you visit the Site.

### INFORMATION USE

We may use the information we collect from your browser or device to:

  * respond to your requests;
  * provide you with information in response to your request;
  * provide support to our Independent Consultants and Members;
  * fulfill orders;
  * operate the Site and customize your experience;
  * provide customized content, advertising, and services;
  * identify or remedy potential threats to the Site’s security;
  * conduct research about your use of the Site and our services; and
  * for any other purpose stated at the time of collection.

### COOKIES

This Site is cookie-enabled to give you a more customized user experience. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are used to collect information on the number of visitors to our site and the number of pages viewed. It is also used to provide relevant information to our visitors and for website and system administration, including research and development, user analysis and business decision-making.

### SHARING INFORMATION

BeautyCounter may share the information we collect with service providers, affiliates, and subsidiaries in connection with the services we provide.

BeautyCounter may share the information collected on this Site with carefully selected marketing partners who may send you information about products and services we think you would enjoy.

If we or some or all of our assets are acquired by another company, including through a sale in connection with bankruptcy, that company will possess the information collected by us, and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your information as described in this Privacy Statement.

We may disclose personally identifiable information or other data to comply with law or legal requirements, enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, or protect our rights, property, or safety of our users, or others.

### Third Party Links

For your convenience, this Site may contain certain hyperlinks to other websites. We make no promises or guarantees regarding data collection on the hyperlinked pages that are not owned by BeautyCounter. We recommend that you read the privacy policy/statement for each site you visit.

### Your choices

We may use the personally identifiable information we collect from you to provide you with opportunities to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like to opt out of future promotional materials from us, you may indicate this preference by following the unsubscribe instructions at the end of such email communications or by contacting us in writing at:

Beautycounter  
1727 Berkeley Street, Studio 1  
Santa Monica, CA 90404

If you would no longer like to receive offers from our marketing partners, you can unsubscribe from additional offers by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each email communication.

### Updates

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Statement. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Statement by updating this page. We encourage you periodically to check this site to learn about the information we collect, use, and share. Your continued use of the Site affirms your agreement to such changes.

### Contact us

Please contact us if you have questions about our Privacy Statement at: info@beautycounter.com
